Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mainstream, Circa 1960s to 1990s; Series 4
  - Individual, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - [Arshkian, Levik], 1974-1984 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - [Artemenko, V.], 1980 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - [Artiunian, Eduard, Marzpeta, and Shagen], 1978 February 10-1981 December 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - [Artsimovich, Viktor], 1983 April 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - [Artsishevskaia, Kristina], 1971 December 28-1972 May 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - [Arutiunian, Shagen], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - [Assel'baums, Teodor], 1977 July 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - [Avagian, Sirvard], 1981 April 16-1982 July 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - [Avgust, Aleksandr], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - [Azadovskii, Konstantin], 1980 December-1982 September 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - [Azarkh, Aleksandra], 1980 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - [Azbel, Mark], 1977 October-1981 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - [Azernikov, Boris], 1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - [Babarika, Lidia], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - [Babich, Sergei], 1976 August 4-1976 August 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - [Akhterov, Vladimir Tiumily], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [Babin, Oktiabr'], 1978 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - [Babitskii, Andrei], 1990 April 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - [Babitskii, Konstantin], 1968 October 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - [Babitsky, Fyodor], 1981 March 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - [Badz'o, Iurii (Georgii)?], 1979 November-1988 August 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - [Bagdavadze, Miriam], 1982 May 26-1982 July 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - [Baikal'skii, D.], 1976 September 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Bakhmin [Vyacheslav], 1978-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bakhmin [Vyacheslav], 1978-1985; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bakhmin [Vyacheslav], 1970-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Balakhonov [Vladimir], 1976-1985; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Balakhonov [Vladimir], 1974-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - [Balovlenkov, Iurii], 1982 February 28-1985 July 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - [Baltsvinik, Mikhail], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - [Barabanov, Evgeny], 1973 August 25-1975 October 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Baranov [Nikolai], 1980-1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Baranov [Nikolai], 1981-1987; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - [Barats, Vasilii Galina], 1980-1987 March 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - [Barbak, Leonid], 1979 May 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - [Barborovich, Elena], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - [Barinov, Valerii], 1983 January 17-1985 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - [Barkan, Ianis], 1987 February 2-1987 May 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - [Barkhotkina?, Klara], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - [Barladianu, Vasilii], 1977 March-1978 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - [Barmine, Alexander], 1987 December 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - [Basarab, Dmitro], 1976 May 31-1977 June 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - [Bashkirov, Pavel], 1976 July 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - [Batovrin, Sergei], 1982 June 5-1983 September 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - [Batyrshin, Vladimir], 1987 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - [Bazderov, Vladimir], 1987 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - [Bebko, Vladislav], 1980 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - [Bedarev, Viktor], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - [Begun, Iosef], 1977 May 20-1987 September 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - [Beilina, Dina], 1977 December 1-1978 July 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - [Beizer, Mikhail], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - [Beliakov, Georgii], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - [Belogorodskaia, Irina], 1969 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - [Belov, Iurii], 1977 June 29-1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - [Belov, Sergei], 1980-1987 May 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - [Bentsel', V.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - [Berdnyk, Oles'], 1979 December 27-1984 July 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - [Berman, Grigory], 1973 September 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - [Bernshtam, Mikhail], 1976 May 10-1977 January 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - [Bieliauskiene, Jadvuge], 1983 May 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - [Bitov, Oleg], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - [Blinov, Iurii], 1977 September 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - [Bliumin, Genadii], 1987 August 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - [Blokhin, Tatiana], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - [Blonsky, Jill], 1985 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - [Bogachev, V. M.], 1983 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - [Bogaraz, Larissa Iosif], 1969 June 20-1988 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - [Bogatyrev, Konstantin], 1974 February 20-1979 May 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - [Bogdanov, Sasha], 1988 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - [Bogdanov, Vasilii], 1989 July 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - [Bogoliubov, Gennadii], 1976 November-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - [Bogolovskii, Aleksandr], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - [Bogometov, Mikhail], 1989 June 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - [Bogushis, Vitautas], 1987 November 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - [Boiarovskaia, Tamara], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - [Boiko, Nikolai], 1982 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - [Bokov, Nikolai], 1974 January 25-1979 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - [Bolkhovskoi, Mikhail], 1979 May 25-1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - [Bolonkin, Aleksandr], 1974 February 2-1986 July 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - [Bombin, Mikhail], 1986 October 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - [Bondar, Nikolai], 1976 February 24-1978 January 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - [Borisov, Kolia], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - [Borisov, Vadim], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Vlad[imir] Borisov, 1969-1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - VIE Borisov [Vladimir], 1967-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - [Borodin, Leonid], 1977 January 11-1983 May 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - [Borodin, Nikolai], 1985 September 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - [Borovskoi, Viktor], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - [Botov, Nikolai], 1986 April 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - [Brailovskii, Viktor], 1979 January 10-1981 June 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - [Braun, Nikolai], 1974 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - [Brengauz, Yury], 1980 December 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - [Brezhneva, Galina], 1987; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - [Brodsky, Iosif], 1964 August 31-1987 December 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - [Brodsky, Vladimir], 1985 July 15-1986 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - [Bronskii, Lev], 1990; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - [Bublik, Viktor], 1978 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - [Bubuian, Asia], 1977 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - [Buianov, Mikhail], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - [Bukharina, N.], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - [Bukov, Vasily], 1988 January 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Bukovsky [,Vladimir] [1/5], 1974-1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bukovsky [,Vladimir] [2/5], 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bukovsky [,Vladimir] [3/5], 1972-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bukovsky [,Vladimir] [4/5], 1974-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bukovsky [,Vladimir] [5/5], 1967-1973; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - [Bulakh, Eduard], 1981 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - [Bulakh, Svetlana], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - [Bulgakov, Mikhail], 1980 February 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - [Bumeisters, Juris], 1981 October 20-1981 December 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - [Burmistrovich, Il'a], 1969 May 21-1969 December 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - [Burtsev, Iurii], 1980 September 4-1980 September 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - [Butaev, Vladimir], 1986 September 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - [Butkin, Vladimir], 1981 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - [Butman, Gilel'], 1975 January 25-1976 June 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - [Butov, Petr], 1982 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - [Buzinnikov, Evgenii], 1978 May 18-1979 January 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Chalidze [,Valery], 1970-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - [Chebykina, L. I.], 1985 May 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - [Chekalin, Aleksandr], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - [Chekalkina, Raisa], 1981 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - [Chekanavichius, Arvydas], 1983 February 7-1979 April 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - [Chemiakin, Mikhail], 1985 March 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - [Chermykhin, Sergei], 1978 July-1979 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - [Cheriev, Aleksandr], 1987 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - [Cherkasov, Anatoly], 1985 August 22-1986 December 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - [Cherkov, Nikoai], 1979 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - [Chernikova, L.], 1949-1989; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - [Chernishov, Vasilii], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - [Chernobylskii, Boris], 1981 May 19-1981 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - [Chernov, Anatolii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - [Cherny, Osip], 1974 February 13-1976 November 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - [Chernyshev, Boris], 1986 September 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - [Chertin, Aleksandr], 1977 September 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - [Chertkova, Anna], 1973 December-1980 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - [Cheverov, Viktor], 1979 February 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - [Cheverov, Vitalii], 1984 May 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - [Chornovil, Vechislav], 1968 February 11-1983 January 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - [Vicheslav Maximovich] Chornovil - Appeal, 1978 March 10-1999 March 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - [Chramov, Nikolai], 1985 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - [Chudnovskii, David], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - [Chuiko, Bogdan], 1977 May-1983 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - [Chukaevy, Aleksandr Larisa], 1986 January 3-1986 May 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - [Chukovskaia, Lidiia], 1966-1981 May 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - [Chulkov, Olga Irina], 1984 January 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - [Churdyntsev, Ivan], 1977 January 27-1977 February 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - [Churkin, V. S.], 1977 July 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - [Chursina, Galina], 1981 July 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - [Cidzikas, Petras], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - [Costakis, George], 1981 November 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - [Danchev, Vladimir], 1983 June 2-1983 August 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Daniel (Yuly Larissa) Sinyavsky [Andrei], 1965-1973; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - +A[lexander,] Yuli + L[arissa] Daniel [1/2], 1965-1988; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - +A[lexander,] Yuli + L[arissa] Daniel [2/2], 1969-1988; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - [Daniliuk, Ivan], 1988 February 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - [Darr, Aleks], 1983 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - [Daverashvili, Boris], 1974 December 23-1975 April 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Viktor Davidov, 1983-1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - [Davidovich, Bella], 1982 May 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - [Davydov, Egor], 1975 October 20-1979 May 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - [Davydov, Vasilii], 1978 April 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - [Davydov, Viktor], 1985 April 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Davydov, Viktor, 1981-1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - [Debryansky, Yevgenia], 1988 February 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - [Dedekaev, Sergei], 1987 November 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - [Degner, Margarita], 1973; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - [Deich, Mark], 1981-1986 October 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - [Delone, Vadim], 1968 October 11-1969 August 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - [Dem'ianov, B.], 1987 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - [Dem'ianov, Nikolai], 1979 May 4-1979 June 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - [Denisov, Iurii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - [Deriugin, Vladimir], 1976 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - [D'iachenko, __________], 1981 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - [Diad'kin, Iosef], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - [Didenko, Sergei], 1978 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - [Diment, Igor], 1972 February 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - [Dimshitz, Mark], 1973 August 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - [Dobrov, Leonid], 1988 April 16-1988 May 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - [Dobrovol'skii, Aleksei], 1958 August 5-1968 June 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - [Dolgachev, Ivan], 1971 December 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - [Dolgii, Vladimir], 1973 September 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - [Dolgoter, Iakov], 1978 February 9-1978 March 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - [Doryina, Lidia], 1983 January 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - [Dremliuga, Vladimir], 1968 October 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - [Drobitskii, Eduard], 1985 December 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - [Drot, Raesa Karmela Raiz], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - [Drugova, Alla], 1978 May 27-1978 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - [Druk, Vassili], 1981 December 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - [Druskin, Lev], 1980 June 25-1982 January 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - [Dubinets, Nikolai], 1978 February 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - [Dubinetskie, Petr Nina], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Dubrovs, [Andrei + Aleksander], 1972-1985; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - [Dudinskii, Igor'], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - [Dudkin, Lev], 1983 February 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Dudko [Dmitriy], 1977 April 27-1981 May 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Fr. D[mitry] Dudko, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - [Duduk, Halyna], 1980 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - [Dulerain, Yurii], 1974 February 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - [Dvoretskii, Ivan], 1975 November 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - [Dymko, Teodor], 1976-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - [Dytiuk, Nikolai], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Dzhemilev [Mustafa], 1968-1985; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - [Dzhemilev, Reshat Mustafa], 1976 April 15-1987 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - [Dziuba, Ivan Iurii], 1971 April 27-1981 December 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - [Ebel' Family], 1978 June-1980 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - [Edel'shteina, Iuliana], 1986 July 29-1986 December 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - [Egle, Il'ia], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - [Eidel'man, Natan], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - [Eiskaya, Nadezhda], 1978 November 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - [Ekkel Family], 1977 December 19-1979 December 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - [Elistratov, Viktor], 1979 July-1986 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - [Eltsin, Boris], 1986 March 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - [Enver, Ametov], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - [Eodekov], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - [Ermakov, Georgii], 1974 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - [Ermolaev, Sergei], 1977-1987 August 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - [Errero, Ramires], 1988 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - [Ershov, Mikhail], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - [Esenin-Volpin, Akeksandr], 1968; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - [Etkind, Efim], 1974 April 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - [Evdokimov, Rostislav], 1976 September 3-1987 January 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - [Evgrafov, N.A.], 1975 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - [Evsiukov, Serafim], 1979 June-1985 April 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - [Evtushyenko, Evgeny], 1974 February 19-1988 June 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - [Evus, Dmitrii], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - [Ezhov, I.], 1973 November 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - [Fain, Veniamin], 1977 May 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Fainberg, [Victor], 1969 April 9-1977 September 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - [Fedorchuk, Vitalii], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - [Fedorov, Iurii], 1972 May 21-1982 July 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - [Fedotov, Eduard], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - [Fedotov, Ivan], 1980 March 21-1982 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - [Fedroenko, Vasyl], 1976 August 15-1977 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - [Fefelov, Valerii], 1978 February 11-1982 January 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - [Feigina, Fira], 1978 August 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - [Fel'dman, Aleksandr], 1973-1977 April 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - [Fel'dman, Grigorii], 1986 October 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - [Feofanov, Iurii], 1983 July; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - [Fesh, Mariia], 1987 December 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - [Filatov, Anatolii], 1978 July 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - [Filimonov, Vadim], 1976 December 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - [Filippov, Andrei], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - [Finkel', Fedor], 1982 December 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - [Fisher, Vladimir], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - [Fleishgakker, Vladimir], 1982 February 18-1982 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - [Flerovy, Inessa Viktor], 1986 March 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - [Fonchenkov, Vasilii], 1980 May 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - [Foshin, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - [Fradkova, Nadia], 1984 June 16-1985 March 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - [Freiman, Grigori], 1983 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - [Freisen, Ida], 1981 June 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - [Frenkel', Vladimir], 1985 March 7-1985 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - [Gabai, Il'ia], 1969 August 21-1977 September 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - [Gabak, D.], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - [Gaiauskas, Balis], 1977-1985 October 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - [Gaidamachuk, Ekaterina], 1985 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - [Gaiduk, Roman], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - [Gajauskas, Balys], 1981 June 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - [Galanskov, Iurii], 1963 April 8-1973 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - [Yuri] Galanskov [Alexander] Ginsburg Trial, 1967-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - [Galenskii, Rostislav], 1980 July 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - [Galetskii, Rostislav], 1978 February 9-1982 March 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - [Galich, Aleksandr], 1972 January 21-1978 April 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - [Zviad] Gamsakhurdia [Merab] Kostava [1/2], 1974-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - [Zviad] Gamsakhurdia [Merab] Kostava [2/2], 1969-1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Gamsakhurdia [Zviad], Kostava [Merab], Morchadze [G.] [1/2], 1977-1988; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Gamsakhurdia [Zviad], Kostava [Merab], Morchadze [G.] [2/2], 1975-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - [Gandziuk, Vladimir], 1976 October 8-1978 June 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - [Ganiushkin, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - [Gankin, Valentin], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - [Gastev, Iurii], 1976 January-1981 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - [Gefter, Mikhail], 1979 November 26-1980 January 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - [Gel', Ivan], 1976 August 7-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - [Gendin, Lev], 1977 November 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - [Gendler, Iurii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - [Genelin, Vyachislav], 1982 February 5-1982 February 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 24, Folder 9)